Guide to the Cable 13 Videotapes, 1976-2009 UA.09.13.0008
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Accession UA2016-0027, 1976-2009; 2
  - Interview: Zola Levitt at Duke, 1995 March 02 (Box 75, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0920)
    Cable13 tape number: Tape 1 (4); Other notes: 139 Soc. Sci.
  - Interview: Zola Levitt at Duke, 1995 March 02 (Box 76, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0921)
    Cable13 tape number: Tape 2 (4); Other notes: 139 Soc. Sci.
  - Interview: Zola Levitt at Duke, 1995 March 02 (Box 76, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0922)
    Cable13 tape number: Tape 3 (4); Other notes: 139 Soc. Sci.
  - Interview: Zola Levitt at Duke, 1995 March 02 (Box 76, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0923)
    Cable13 tape number: Tape 4 (4); Other notes: 139 Soc. Sci.
  - Sexpressions: Communicate w/ Partner, 1995 March 08 (Box 74, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0924)
    Program Length: 33mins56secs; Other notes: "How to Communicate w/ Your Partner" Hosts: Margie Menza, Susie Stewart
  - Caveat Emptor, 1995 March 13 (Box 103, Video-cassette UA09130008-VHS-0050)
    Program Length: 17mins30secs; Other notes: Directed by Michael Mitchell
  - Burger King Eating Contest, 1995 March 28 (Box 75, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0925)
    Program Length: 8mins10secs
  - For the Woman of Color, 1995 March 29 (Box 71, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0926)
    Program Length: 26mins17secs; Cable13 tape number: Master; Other notes: Crew: Robin Hamilton, Stacy Ebron
  - Still Life with Foucault, 1995 April 05 (Box 70, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0899)
    Other notes: Foucault: A Reader, Crew: James Bower, Christie Herring
  - Sexpressions: No Sex & Relationships, 1995 April 12 (Box 72, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0900)
    Other notes: Last Show
  - Blue Traveler, 1995 April 20 (Box 71, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0901)
    Program Length: 30mins23secs; Cable13 tape number: Ep #1; Other notes: Host: Linda Frey, Dir: Danielle Lemmon
  - Duke Legends Game, 1995 September 08 (Box 61, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0932)
    Cable13 tape number: Tape 1 (3); Other notes: Crew: Jonathan Segal, Commentator: Steve Ross
  - Duke Legends Game, 1995 September 08 (Box 62, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0933)
    Cable13 tape number: Tape 2 (3); Other notes: Crew: Jonathan Segal, Commentator: Steve Ross
  - Duke Legends Game, 1995 September 08 (Box 62, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0934)
    Cable13 tape number: Tape 3 (3); Other notes: Crew: Jonathan Segal, Commentator: Steve Ross
  - Rutgers at Duke (Football), 1995 September 09 (Box 96, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0935)
    Program Length: 30mins5secs; Other notes: First 3 quarters, Crew: Anne Felten, J. Shannon Gatlin
  - Safety at Duke, 1995 September 11 (Box 79, Video-cassette UA09130008-Bcam-0004)
    Other notes: A C13 special
  - "Collective Soul," "The Pharcyde," "The Roots", 1995 September 15, 1996 March 29 (Box 86, Video-cassette UA09130008-Bcam-0005)
    Program Length: 15mins; Other notes: 3/29/96-Live from Cameron Indoor Stadium, 9/15/95-Live from Few Quad, Crew: Stephen Zapotoczny, Z-Squad Prod, Duke Cable 13
  - Blue vs. White Game, 1995 October 28 (Box 77, Video-cassette UA09130008-Bcam-0006)
    Other notes: Live from cis, Prod: Jonathan Segal, Shannon Gatlins
  - Cameron Corner, 1995 October 30 (Box 76, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0931)
    Program Length: 21mins34secs; Cable13 tape number: Tape #1; Other notes: Host: Steven Ross
  - Joan Osborne & Rusted Root Concert, 1995 November 02 (Box 88, Video-cassette UA09130008-Bcam-0007)
    Cable13 tape number: Part 1 (3); Other notes: Finale and encore
  - Joan Osborne & Rusted Root Concert, 1995 November 02 (Box 89, Video-cassette UA09130008-Bcam-0008)
    Cable13 tape number: Part 2 (3); Other notes: End of Joan and beginning of Rusted Root
  - Joan Osborne & Rusted Root Concert, 1995 November 02 (Box 89, Video-cassette UA09130008-Bcam-0009)
    Cable13 tape number: Part 3 (3); Other notes: Rusted Root
  - SideVision, 1995 November 06 (Box 73, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0927)
    Program Length: 17mins30secs; Cable13 tape number: Ep #1; Other notes: Renter's Rights
  - Cameron Corner, 1995 November 13 (Box 79, Video-cassette UA09130008-Bcam-0010)
    Cable13 tape number: #2; Other notes: AIA Highlights, Roundtable: Seth Kreger, Dan Cohen, Emily Coleman, Toby Ast
  - Cameron Corner, 1995 December 04 (Box 79, Video-cassette UA09130008-Bcam-0011)
    Program Length: 31mins52secs; Cable13 tape number: #3; Other notes: Brisbane, Alaska Shootout (ODU, Indiana, Iowa) Illinois highlights, Michigan Preview, Jason Ross Interview, Host: Steven Ross
  - SC State vs Duke, 1995 December 04 (Box 100, Video-cassette UA09130008-Bcam-0012)
    Cable13 tape number: 2
  - "The Best of Night Night" Master, 1996 May (Box 68, Video-cassette UA09130008-Bcam-0040)
    Program Length: 29mins; Cable13 tape number: 93734; Other notes: Crew: David Lammey, Steve Z.
  - Diwali, 1996 (Box 68, Video-cassette UA09130008-Bcam-0055)
  - Diwali, 1996 (Box 68, Video-cassette UA09130008-Bcam-0056)
    Program Length: 22mins10secs; Cable13 tape number: Tape 2 (2)
  - Diwali, 1996 (Box 68, Video-cassette UA09130008-Bcam-0057)
    Other notes: Jon Segal
  - Duke Men's Soccer vs UNC, 1996 (Box 78, Video-cassette UA09130008-Bcam-0058)
  - Duke Men's Soccer vs UNC, 1996 (Box 78, Video-cassette UA09130008-Bcam-0059)
  - Ivy Tower-"Hard Times", 1996 (Box 81, Video-cassette UA09130008-Bcam-0060)
    Program Length: 40mins; Cable13 tape number: E 4; Other notes: Prod: Danielle Lemmon, Seth Squadron, Stephen Zapotoczny, Z-squad, Cable 13
  - Ivy Tower-"Last Daze", 1996 (Box 81, Video-cassette UA09130008-Bcam-0061)
    Cable13 tape number: E 5; Other notes: Prod: Danielle Lemmon, Seth Squadron, Stephen Zapotoczny, Z-squad, Cable 13
  - "OS Males after the Revolt of 1835", 1996 (Box 85, Video-cassette UA09130008-Bcam-0062)
    Cable13 tape number: Part 1; Other notes: African Muslim Survival in Salvador, Bahia, Brazil Prod: Zaid Abdul-Aleem
  - "OS Males after the Revolt of 1835", 1996 (Box 85, Video-cassette UA09130008-Bcam-0063)
    Cable13 tape number: Part 2; Other notes: African Muslim Survival in Salvador, Bahia, Brazil Prod: Zaid Abdul-Aleem
  - Honduras Master, 1996 (Box 86, Video-cassette UA09130008-Bcam-0064)
    Program Length: 25mins; Other notes: Chris Sims
  - Ivy Tower - Class, 1996 (Box 99, Video-cassette UA09130008-Bcam-0065)
    Program Length: 37mins; Cable13 tape number: Ep 2; Other notes: Prod: Danielle Lemmon, Seth Squadron, Stephen Zapotoczny, Z-squad, Cable 13
  - Duke Yearlook & Tangled up in Blue Promo, 1996, 1997 (Box 94, Video-cassette UA09130008-Bcam-0066)
    Program Length: 34min&3mins; Other notes: Prod: Bob Hackett
  - Duke vs Athletes in Action, 1996-1997 (Box 78, Video-cassette UA09130008-Bcam-0067)
    Cable13 tape number: Tape 1; Other notes: Live Cable 13 Broadcast
  - Duke vs Athletes in Action, 1996-1997 (Box 78, Video-cassette UA09130008-Bcam-0068)
  - Cameron Corner, 1996-1997 (Box 79, Video-cassette UA09130008-Bcam-0069)
    Program Length: 42mins; Cable13 tape number: #1; Other notes: Guests: Dan Cohen, Jonathan Gmz, Seth Kreger, Host: Steve Ross
  - Cameron Corner, 1996-1997 (Box 80, Video-cassette UA09130008-Bcam-0070)
    Program Length: 35mins; Cable13 tape number: #2; Other notes: Guests: Sheri Sauter, Grumpy old Duke fan, Host: Steven Ross (DSG Head Line Monitor)
  - Joe's Music Playground, 1996-1997 (Box 83, Video-cassette UA09130008-Bcam-0071)
    Cable13 tape number: S2/E1.5
  - Joe's Music Playground, 1996-1997 (Box 83, Video-cassette UA09130008-Bcam-0072)
    Program Length: 23mins; Cable13 tape number: S2/E1
  - Joe's Music Playground, 1996-1997 (Box 83, Video-cassette UA09130008-Bcam-0073)
    Cable13 tape number: S2/E5
  - Joe's Music Playground, 1996-1997 (Box 84, Video-cassette UA09130008-Bcam-0074)
    Program Length: 34mins; Cable13 tape number: S2/E3 Tape 1
  - Joe's Music Playground, 1996-1997 (Box 84, Video-cassette UA09130008-Bcam-0075)
    Cable13 tape number: S2/E3 Tape 2
  - Joe's Music Playground, 1996-1997 (Box 84, Video-cassette UA09130008-Bcam-0076)
    Cable13 tape number: S2/E8
  - Joe's Music Playground, 1996-1997 (Box 84, Video-cassette UA09130008-Bcam-0077)
    Cable13 tape number: S2/E9
  - Joe's Music Playground, 1996-1997 (Box 84, Video-cassette UA09130008-Bcam-0078)
    Cable13 tape number: S2/E11
  - Joe's Music Playground, 1996-1997 (Box 84, Video-cassette UA09130008-Bcam-0079)
    Cable13 tape number: S2/E12
  - Joe's Music Playground, 1996-1997 (Box 84, Video-cassette UA09130008-Bcam-0080)
    Cable13 tape number: S2/E12 Tape 2; Other notes: "Mercury Night"
  - Joe's Music Playground, 1996-1997 (Box 87, Video-cassette UA09130008-Bcam-0081)
    Cable13 tape number: S2/E10
  - Blue-White Scrimmage, 1996-1997 (Box 89, Video-cassette UA09130008-Bcam-0082)
    Program Length: 22mins28secs; Cable13 tape number: Tape 2 (2)
  - Davy Crockett & American Mythology, 1996 Spring (Box 74, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0944)
    Program Length: 14mins35secs; Other notes: "Disney's David Crockett and American Mythology" by David Sirolly
  - Duke University 1996 Yearlook (Box 92, Video-cassette UA09130008-VHS-0024)
    Program Length: 35mins
  - Ivy Tower - Class, 1996 (Box 92, Video-cassette UA09130008-VHS-0025)
    Program Length: 40mins; Cable13 tape number: Ep 2; Other notes: Prod: Danielle Lemmon, Seth Squadron, Stephen Zapotoczny, Z-squad, Cable 13
  - Ivy Tower - Hard Times, 1996 (Box 92, Video-cassette UA09130008-VHS-0026)
    Program Length: 40mins; Cable13 tape number: Ep 4; Other notes: Prod: Danielle Lemmon, Seth Squadron, Stephen Zapotoczny, Z-squad, Cable 13
  - Ivy Tower - Last Daze, 1996 (Box 92, Video-cassette UA09130008-VHS-0027)
    Program Length: 40mins; Cable13 tape number: Ep 5; Other notes: Prod: Danielle Lemmon, Seth Squadron, Stephen Zapotoczny, Z-squad, Cable 13
  - Duke Yearlook, 1996 (Box 95, Video-cassette UA09130008-VHS-0028)
    Program Length: 35mins; Other notes: Prod: Robert J. Hackett, Jr.
  - Tracking Signal Impulse Movie, 1996 (Box 103, Video-cassette UA09130008-VHS-0029)
    Other notes: Ã‚Â© Adam Joyce All rights reserved
  - Ivy Tower - Class, 1996 (Box 103, Video-cassette UA09130008-VHS-0030)
  - Ivy Tower - Hard Times, 1996 (Box 103, Video-cassette UA09130008-VHS-0031)
    Cable13 tape number: Ep 4; Other notes: Z-Squad Prod, Duke U. Cable 13
  - 5th News Show, 1996 April (Box 103, Video-cassette UA09130008-VHS-0052)
  - AGO AME, 1996 Fall (Box 103, Video-cassette UA09130008-VHS-0053)
    Program Length: 17mins; Cable13 tape number: CA 180s; Other notes: by students of Anne Allison and Marco Williams
  - Kammerer Copy, 1996-1997 (Box 95, Video-cassette UA09130008-VHS-0055)
  - Kammerer Submissions, 1996-1997 (Box 97, Video-cassette UA09130008-VHS-0056)
  - Ivy Tower - Hard Times, 1996 (Box 103, Video-cassette UA09130008-VHS-0087)
  - Cameron Corner, 1996 January 29 (Box 79, Video-cassette UA09130008-Bcam-0028)
    Program Length: 37mins; Cable13 tape number: #6; Other notes: Chris Collins Interview, Temple Highlights, Roundtable: Emily Coleman, Toby Ast, Dan Cohen
  - Cameron Corner, 1996 February 06 (Box 93, Video-cassette UA09130008-Bcam-0029)
    Program Length: 36mins37secs; Cable13 tape number: #7; Other notes: Krzyzewskiville Tour, Maryland, UNC, Clemson Highlights, Host: Steven Ross
  - Jennifer Frayson-Interview w/ Justin Dillon, 1996 February 16 (Box 96, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0940)
    Program Length: 22mins45secs
  - Wendell Theater/Laurie Carr Interviews, 1996 February 20 (Box 101, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0941)
    Cable13 tape number: 1st show; Other notes: Wendell Theater Raw Footage, Laurie Carr interviews members/directors/producer of the Fantasticks, 1st show
  - News Show #1, 1996 February 21 (Box 81, Video-cassette UA09130008-Bcam-0030)
    Cable13 tape number: 9
  - D.S.G. Presidential Debate, 1996 February 24 (Box 86, Video-cassette UA09130008-Bcam-0031)
    Cable13 tape number: Tape 1 (2); Other notes: Milan and Jeff
  - D.S.G. Presidential Debate, 1996 February 24 (Box 86, Video-cassette UA09130008-Bcam-0032)
    Cable13 tape number: Tape 2 (2); Other notes: Milan and Jeff
  - News Show #2, 1996 February 28 (Box 81, Video-cassette UA09130008-Bcam-0033)
  - Cameron Corner Cover, 1996 March 02 (Box 26, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0942)
    Other notes: Krzyzewskiville story, Edited Forbes, News Show: Jeff and Suzanne
  - Cameron Corner, 1996 March 25 (Box 79, Video-cassette UA09130008-Bcam-0034)
    Program Length: 37mins; Cable13 tape number: #9; Other notes: Highlights: UNC, Maryland (ACC Tourney), EMU (NCAA), Roundtable: Emily Coleman, Seth Kreger, Dan Cohen, Host: Steven Ross
  - 4th News Show, 1996 March 27 (Box 68, Video-cassette UA09130008-Bcam-0035)
  - Interview w/ Tackus Nesbit, 1996 March 28 (Box 64, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0943)
    Other notes: Interview by Carol Buia (DSG President) Right after elections
  - 5th News Show, 1996 April 03 (Box 86, Video-cassette UA09130008-Bcam-0036)
    Other notes: RB&JH&PH
  - Cornel West, 1996 April 18 (Box 86, Video-cassette UA09130008-Bcam-0037)
  - Cornel West, 1996 April 18 (Box 86, Video-cassette UA09130008-Bcam-0038)
  - Freewater Productions Films Shown, 1996 April 24 (Box 81, Video-cassette UA09130008-Bcam-0039)
    Program Length: 64mins36secs; Other notes: 1.Missing Piece by Rebecca Pryce 2.The Sandwich by Rob Koegler 3.Union Promo by Sam Ware 4.Cinderella's Shoe by Fabrice Lyczba 5.Boxed In by Prerana Reddy 6.A.I. by James Hauser 7.The Fortune Teller by Xavier Marquez 8. Rock-a-bye, bye, bye by Jenny Lynn
  - Full of the Devil, 1996 August 12 (Box 72, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0939)
    Program Length: 18mins; Cable13 tape number: Ep #1; Other notes: Prod: Steve Maynard
  - "Faces in the Crowd", 1996 September 07 (Box 92, Video-cassette UA09130008-VHS-0054)
    Other notes: Premier Performance
  - Duke Off vs Army Def, 1996 September 21 (Box 99, Video-cassette UA09130008-Bcam-0041)
    Cable13 tape number: 1st half
  - Joe's Music Playground, 1996 September 24 (Box 83, Video-cassette UA09130008-Bcam-0042)
    Program Length: 60mins; Cable13 tape number: S2/E2
  - "Faces in the Crowd", 1996 September 27 (Box 81, Video-cassette UA09130008-Bcam-0043)
    Cable13 tape number: Tape 1; Other notes: 1st Performance, Prod: Stephen Zapotoczny, Z-Squad, Cable 13
  - "Faces in the Crowd", 1996 September 27 (Box 81, Video-cassette UA09130008-Bcam-0044)
    Cable13 tape number: Tape 2; Other notes: 1st Performance, Prod: Stephen Zapotoczny, Z-Squad, Cable 13
  - Joe's Music Playground, 1996 October 07 (Box 83, Video-cassette UA09130008-Bcam-0045)
    Program Length: 60mins; Cable13 tape number: S2/E4; Other notes: Guest: Matt Gidney
  - Mike T's Sports Chat, 1996 October 16 (Box 84, Video-cassette UA09130008-Bcam-0046)
    Program Length: 27mins34secs
  - Politix Master 1, 1996 October 30 (Box 84, Video-cassette UA09130008-Bcam-0047)
    Program Length: 24mins46secs; Cable13 tape number: Tape 1 Ep 1; Other notes: Campaign Speeches
  - Politix Master 2, 1996 October 30 (Box 84, Video-cassette UA09130008-Bcam-0048)
    Program Length: 49mins; Cable13 tape number: Tape 2 Ep 1; Other notes: Debate
  - Mike T's Sports Chat, 1996 November 13 (Box 86, Video-cassette UA09130008-Bcam-0049)
    Program Length: 27mins
  - Joe's Music Playground, 1996 November 19 (Box 83, Video-cassette UA09130008-Bcam-0050)
    Cable13 tape number: S2/E6 Tape 1
  - Joe's Music Playground, 1996 November 19 (Box 83, Video-cassette UA09130008-Bcam-0051)
    Cable13 tape number: S2/E6 Tape 2
  - "Faces in the Crowd", 1996 November 22 (Box 81, Video-cassette UA09130008-Bcam-0052)
    Program Length: 44mins; Other notes: Live on TV, Prod: Stephen Zapotoczny, Z-Squad, Cable 13
  - Duke Sports Inferno, 1996 December 04 (Box 89, Video-cassette UA09130008-Bcam-0053)
    Cable13 tape number: Show #1
  - Joe's Music Playground, 1996 December 10 (Box 83, Video-cassette UA09130008-Bcam-0054)
    Program Length: 60mins; Cable13 tape number: S2/E2; Other notes: Live
  - DUI: First Semester Ever, 1997 Spring (Box 78, Video-cassette UA09130008-Bcam-0103)
    Program Length: 30mins; Cable13 tape number: Tape 1 (1); Other notes: Mirecourt Show, Filmed by Jeff Dillinger
  - DUI, 1997 November (Box 90, Video-cassette UA09130008-Bcam-0109)
    Program Length: 60mins; Cable13 tape number: Show #1; Other notes: Final Edit
  - DUI #2, 1997 November (Box 90, Video-cassette UA09130008-Bcam-0110)
    Program Length: 60mins; Other notes: Comedy, Crew: Sean Loughlin, Porter Mason
  - Duke Sports Inferno, 1997 December (Box 99, Video-cassette UA09130008-Bcam-0111)
    Program Length: 29mins58secs; Cable13 tape number: Edition #5; Other notes: submitted for the College Emmys
  - Men's Lacrosse ACC Final Duke vs UVA, 1997 (Box 78, Video-cassette UA09130008-Bcam-0116)
    Other notes: at UVA, HTS Broadcast
  - "Singled Out", 1997 (Box 79, Video-cassette UA09130008-Bcam-0117)
    Other notes: Alchemy Entertainment & Cable 13, Prod: Rob Gehring & Jeff Dillinger
  - Tap Dog Interview, 1997 (Box 85, Video-cassette UA09130008-Bcam-0118)
    Program Length: 34mins; Other notes: Crew: Rob Gehring, Jason Tracey, Ben Epps, Sean Loughlin
  - Safe Rides Confessions, 1997 (Box 85, Video-cassette UA09130008-Bcam-0119)
    Program Length: 29mins; Other notes: Prod: John Tingue, Andrew Kapp
  - "Distant Room", 1997 (Box 86, Video-cassette UA09130008-Bcam-0120)
  - Safe Rides, 1997 (Box 86, Video-cassette UA09130008-Bcam-0121)
    Cable13 tape number: Ep #1
  - The Cable 13 News, 1997 (Box 86, Video-cassette UA09130008-Bcam-0122)
    Program Length: 30mins; Cable13 tape number: Ep #1
  - "Zoo Story" by Edward Albee, 1997 (Box 91, Video-cassette UA09130008-Bcam-0123)
    Program Length: 57mins30secs; Other notes: Presented by Wax Theatre Group, camera: J. Shannon Gatlin
  - Whopper Eating Contest '97, 1997 (Box 98, Video-cassette UA09130008-Bcam-0124)
  - Cable 13 Promos, 1997-1998 (Box 56, Video-cassette UA09130008-Bcam-0125)
    Cable13 tape number: #7; Other notes: (for the open house) Nikki Giovanni
  - Cameron Corner, 1997-1998 (Box 80, Video-cassette UA09130008-Bcam-0126)
    Cable13 tape number: #1
  - Devilvision, 1997-1998 (Box 87, Video-cassette UA09130008-Bcam-0127)
    Cable13 tape number: v.1.01
  - Full of the Devil, 1997 (Box 102, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0063)
    Program Length: 31mins58secs; Cable13 tape number: Ep 1
  - Duke Video Yearbook: Tangled up in Blue, 1997 (Box 95, Video-cassette UA09130008-VHS-0032)
    Program Length: 40mins; Other notes: Prod: Charles W. Saletta Jr., David Toepper
  - Race Day, 1997 (Box 103, Video-cassette UA09130008-VHS-0033)
    Cable13 tape number: Tape #1
  - Cameron Corner, 1997 January 20 (Box 80, Video-cassette UA09130008-Bcam-0083)
    Program Length: 29mins30secs; Cable13 tape number: #4; Other notes: Post Michigan offense analysis, Crew: Steven Ross
  - ACC Basketball UNC vs Duke 1/30/97 1 of 2, 1997 January 30 (Box 98, Video-cassette UA09130008-Bcam-0084)
  - Cameron Corner, 1997 February 03 (Box 89, Video-cassette UA09130008-Bcam-0085)
    Program Length: 60mins2secs; Cable13 tape number: Ep #5; Other notes: Coach K pre-UNC, Pep Rally, UNC game analysis, Host: Steven Ross
  - Duke Sports Inferno, 1997 February 22 (Box 89, Video-cassette UA09130008-Bcam-0086)
    Program Length: 35mins; Cable13 tape number: Show #2; Other notes: Includes feature w/ Nate James, Chris Carrwell & Mike Chapell, Prod: Ben Tishler, Brett Goldberg, Jonathan Segal, Joe Kirmser, Kenan Holly
  - Duke Sports Inferno, 1997 February 22 (Box 89, Video-cassette UA09130008-Bcam-0087)
    Program Length: 35mins; Cable13 tape number: Show #2
  - 14th Annual NC International Jazz Festival, 1997 February 28 (Box 99, Video-cassette UA09130008-Bcam-0088)
    Program Length: 54mins; Other notes: Louie Bellson and the Duke Jazz Ensemble directed by Paul Jeffrey, Prod and Dir by Cable 13 Special Events and DUU Video Yearbook
  - Men's Basketball: Duke vs UNC, 1997 March 02 (Box 94, Video-cassette UA09130008-Bcam-0089)
    Other notes: at UNC
  - Cameron Corner, 1997 March 04 (Box 100, Video-cassette UA09130008-Bcam-0090)
    Program Length: 33mins25secs; Cable13 tape number: #6; Other notes: Post Regular Season roundtable, Host: Steven Ross
  - 1997 DSG Candidate Forum, 1997 March 05 (Box 86, Video-cassette UA09130008-Bcam-0091)
    Other notes: Prod: Laurie Carr, Rob Gehring, Seth Squadron, & Steve Zapotoczny, Sponsors: Cable 13, Independent Students' Association, Spectrum
  - The Screening Room, 1997 March 09 (Box 76, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0948)
    Program Length: 22mins; Cable13 tape number: Ep #1; Other notes: Prod: Jack Parrish
  - The Bob Crossland Show, 1997 March 10 (Box 86, Video-cassette UA09130008-Bcam-0092)
    Program Length: 45mins; Cable13 tape number: Ep #2; Other notes: Crew: Rob Gehring, Benjy Zazove
  - Devil of a Date, 1997 March 12 (Box 85, Video-cassette UA09130008-Bcam-0093)
    Program Length: 29mins5secs; Cable13 tape number: Show #1; Other notes: Crew: Amy Shugar, Darlene Aquino, Jenifer Yen
  - VCR, 1997 March 16 (Box 91, Video-cassette UA09130008-Bcam-0094)
    Program Length: 27mins; Cable13 tape number: Ep #2; Other notes: Master Tape, Prod: Ben Epps, Sean L
  - The Bob Crossland Show, 1997 April 07 (Box 85, Video-cassette UA09130008-Bcam-0095)
    Program Length: 60mins5secs; Cable13 tape number: Ep 3; Other notes: Crew: Rob Gehring, Benjy Zazove
  - Joe's Music Playground, 1997 April 10 (Box 84, Video-cassette UA09130008-Bcam-0096)
    Program Length: 60mins; Cable13 tape number: S2/E14; Other notes: Guest: Matt Gidney
  - Joe's Music Playground, 1997 April 23 (Box 84, Video-cassette UA09130008-Bcam-0097)
    Program Length: 60mins; Cable13 tape number: S2/E15
  - Full of the Devil, 1997 April 23 (Box 101, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0945)
    Program Length: 27mins20secs; Cable13 tape number: Ep 2
  - Devil of a Date w/ commercial, 1997 April 25 (Box 79, Video-cassette UA09130008-Bcam-0098)
    Program Length: 35mins; Cable13 tape number: #2; Other notes: Crew: Amy Shugar, Jen Jeh, Darlene Aquma
  - The Bob Crossland Show, 1997 April 28 (Box 87, Video-cassette UA09130008-Bcam-0099)
    Cable13 tape number: Ep #5; Other notes: Crew: Rob Gehring
  - The Screening Room, 1997 April 28 (Box 77, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0946)
    Program Length: 28mins; Cable13 tape number: Ep #2; Other notes: Prod: Jack Parrish
  - News Show Pilot, 1997 April 29 (Box 81, Video-cassette UA09130008-Bcam-0100)
    Program Length: 35mins; Other notes: Fire in Philippines, A-10 crash, Tobacco ruling, "An Eternity Away," Engineering kegs, Duke Dining, "Guys and Dolls" Student jazz group, sports-NBA playoffs
  - Duke University Graduation Exercises, 1997 May 18 (Box 93, Video-cassette UA09130008-Bcam-0101)
    Cable13 tape number: T1; Other notes: Wallace Wade Stadium
  - Duke University Graduation Exercises, 1997 May 18 (Box 93, Video-cassette UA09130008-Bcam-0102)
    Cable13 tape number: T4; Other notes: Wallace Wade Stadium
  - Cameron Corner, 1997 October 03 (Box 80, Video-cassette UA09130008-Bcam-0104)
    Other notes: Shane Battier, Elton Brand Interview
  - "Sexual Perversity in Chicago", 1997 October 03 (Box 97, Video-cassette UA09130008-Hi8-0001)
    Other notes: 8pm
  - Teller Interview, 1997 October 07 (Box 87, Video-cassette UA09130008-Bcam-0105)
    Program Length: 32mins
  - Blue Vibes, 1997 October 12 (Box 88, Video-cassette UA09130008-Bcam-0106)
    Program Length: 30mins; Cable13 tape number: Show 1; Other notes: Pilot: Part 1
  - Duke Sports Inferno, 1997 October 23 (Box 89, Video-cassette UA09130008-Bcam-0107)
    Program Length: 44mins; Cable13 tape number: Show #4; Other notes: Premier episode of 1997, Trojan Langdon, Kung Fu Theater, creators: Ben Tishler, Brett Goldberg, Prod: Jonathan Segal, Kenan Holley